Their Footage. Your Nightmare.
Conjuring Tapes is a horror, mystery film directed by Randy Nundlall Jr..
While sorting through their late friend's belongings, two women discover VHS tapes showing them in haunting,
unfamiliar scenes, each one drawing them into the grasp of a mysterious, malevolent entity.
Sam, played by Samantha Laurenti.
Molly, played by Brenda Yanez.
Jason, played by Daniel Outlaw.
Gary, played by Robert Felsted Jr..
Greg, played by Greg Sestero.
Ghost, played by Whitney Clack.
The Conjuring Universe is an American horror franchise and shared
universe centered on a series of supernatural horror films.
The franchise is produced by New Line Cinema, Atomic Monster, and
the Safran Company, and distributed by Warner Bros.
The films present a dramatization of the supposedly real-life adventures of Ed and Lorraine Warren,
paranormal investigators and authors associated with prominent yet controversial cases of haunting.
The main series follows their attempts to help people harassed by spirits, while the spin-off
films focus on the origins of some of the entities the Warrens have encountered.
The franchise has been commercially successful, grossing $2.7 billion against a combined
budget of $263 million and becoming the highest-grossing horror franchise to date.
The franchise has received mixed reviews.
The film explores themes of evil, found footage, mysterious
events, malevolent spirit, paranormal horror.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.